Olga Molchanova

Junior Full Stack Developer

PROFILE

I am Junior Full Stack Developer, focused on HTML, CSS, JS, React, TypeScript, Node.js. I have done successfull team projects and idividual ones. My goal is to get a job in a reputed company where I can use my skills and knowledge to deliver good results in the long term. Always ready to learn and gain new experiences.

PROJECT EXPERIENCE

Energy Flow (GitHub)

Team project

Sheduler of training programs allowing to do sports independently (HTML, CSS, JS, Vite). Role: developer of exercise modal and partly of rating modal.

FocusFrame (GitHub)

Team project

Foto school offering different types of courses in photography (HTML, CSS, JS). Role: developer of mobile modal.

WebStudio (GitHub)

Individual project

The site was created for the company "WebStudio". Adaptive design, transformation effects, modal windows (HTML, SCSS, JS).

See more my projects at mysite...

WORK EXPERIENCE

Senior chemist chromatographer

Vitamin Plant of Kyiv

2016 - present

- Working with documentation, including foreign sources
- Planning, research and development of drug analysis methods
- Training of junior specialists
- Compliance with deadlines
- Teamwork skills

Laboratory assistant

Pharmaceutical Company Darnytsia

2015 - 2016

- Working width a PC and specific software
- Working with reagents, laboratory equipment and instruments

Cashier seller in the supermarket

2014 - 2015

• Communication skills width customers

+38(096)89-05-772

designer.molchanova@gmail.com

Kyiv City, Ukraine

linkedin.com

github.com

<u>mysite</u>

TECH SKILLS

Web Technologies & Tools

- JavaScript (ES6)
- HTML
- CSS
- React
- Node.js
- Type Script
- VS Code
- Git
- GitHub
- Vite
- Vercel
- SCSS
- Figma

SOFT SKILLS

- Team work
- Deadline orienting
- Attention to detail
- Communication

EDUCATION

IT School GoIT

2023 - 2024

Fullstack Developer

Taras Shevchenko National University of Kyiv

2009 - 2015

Master's degree

Chemist, scientist

LENGUAGES

- English Pre-Intermediate
- Ukrainian Native